Robert R. Simmons Papers
© 2007 University of Connecticut
Robert R. Simmons Papers.
undated, 1991-2006.
Archives & Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center.
Simmons, Robert R.
174.2 linear feet.
Records documenting the early legislative career of Robert R. "Rob" Simmons. Simmons represented Stonington and North Stonington from 1991 to 2001 in the Connecticut General Assembly before his election to Congress, representing Connecticut's Second Congressional District from 2001 until 2007. He was nominated as Connecticut's first Business Advocate by Governor M. Jodi Rell in February 2007, and in April was unanimously confirmed by both houses of the General Assembly.
MSS20070029
Biography
Robert R. Simmons was born in New York, NY, on 11 February 1943. He graduated from Haverford College (Haverford, PA in 1965 and received his M.P.A. from Harvard University (Cambridge, MA) in 1979. Simmons was drafted by the U.S. Army as a Private in 1965, attended Infantry Officer Candidate School and served in Vietnam for twenty months where he won two Bronze Star Medals. He served in the Army Reserves from 1969-2003 retiring as a Colonel. For ten years he was an operations officer in the Central Intelligence Agency (1969-1979) before joining the staff of United States Senator John Chafee (Rhode Island). In 1981, he joined the staff of the Senate Intelligence Committee where he served as Staff Director for Senator Barry Goldwater (Arizona) from 1981-1985. He served five terms in the Connecticut General Assembly (1991-2001) before his election to the U.S. Congress in 2000, representing the second district from 3 January 2001 until until January 2007. In February 2007, Simmons was nominated by Governor M. Jodi Rell to be Connecticut's first Business Advocate.
He is married to Edith P. "Heidi" Simmons, also of Stonington, and has a daughter Jane and a son Robert.
Scope and Content
The collection contains subject and chronological files maintained by Simmons during his years in the Connecticut General Assembly.
Arrangement
The box inventory is listed as received.
Series I: Files ( undated, 1991-2006 ) contains administrative files pertaining to Simmons' activities in the Connecticut general assembly.
Related Material
Archives & Special Collections has a substantial collection of materials pertaining to Connecticut politics. For detailed information on these collections please contact the curator or ask at the reference desk.
Index Terms
This record series is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Persons:
Simmons, Robert R.
Organizations:
Connecticut--General Assembly--House of Representatives--Members' papers.
Places:
Connecticut--Politics and government.
Subjects:
Politicians--Connecticut.; Legislators--United States.; Legislators--Connecticut.
Document Types:
Correspondence.; Administrative Records.; Financial Records.; Minutes.; Press releases.; Photocopies.; Notes.; Speeches.; Newsletters.; Newspapers.
Occupations:
Restrictions on Access
There are no access restrictions on this collection.
Acquisition Information
The materials were donated by Mr. Simmons in 2007.
Detailed Description
- Series I: Files, undated, 1991-2006
  - Subject Files, A - B, undated (Box 1)
  - Subject Files, C - G, undated (Box 2)
  - Subject Files, G - N, undated (Box 3)
  - Subject Files, O - S, undated (Box 4)
  - Subject Files, S - T, undated (Box 5)
  - Speech and Case files, undated (Box 7)
  - Chronological file, 1991 July - 1993 June (Box 8)
  - Chronological file, 1993 July - 1996 July (Box 9)
  - Chronological file, 1996 August - 2000 July (Box 10)
  - Jonathan Martin Files, undated (Box 11)
  - Defense Issues, undated (Box 12)
  - Constituent correspondence, undated (Box 13)
  - Coast Guard, T & I, undated (Box 15)
  - Clippings, undated (Box 16)
  - Education files, undated (Box 18)
  - Appropriations, undated (Box 20)
  - Labor and BRAC, undated, 2001-2006 (Box 21)
    - Unions and CFR, undated
    - Minimum wage and other wage issues, undated
    - AFL-CIO, undated
    - Steel, undated
    - Project Labor Agreements, undated
    - Associated Builders and Contractors, undated
    - Fast Track and Labor, undated
    - Workers Bill of Rights, undated
    - Ergonomics and workplace safety, undated
    - Labor, undated
    - Firefighters, undated
    - Cross Sound Ferry Services, undated
    - Meet and Greet, 2005 March 18
    - Connecticut Labor, undated
    - Amerbelle, undated
    - Labor and HSD issues, undated
    - Unemployment, undated
    - Pratt & Whitney, undated
    - Fenn vs. CWA (Local 1298), undated
    - National Association of Govenment Employees, 2003
    - Office Manual, 2002
    - Navy firefighters, 2005
    - Elderly housing problems, 2004
    - Firefighters tax abatements, 2006
    - GrowJobsCT Advisory Board, 2006
    - GrowJobsCT, 2005
    - Building and Construction Trades Council, 2005
    - Connecticut AFL-CIO, 2005
    - Veterans Workfroce Development, 2005
    - Correspondence, undated
    - Airline poliots, 2005
    - Association of Letter Carriers, 2005
    - Construction trades, 2004-2005
    - FAA, 2006
    - Electric Boat Workman's Compensation, 2003
    - Firefighters, 2006
    - Hamilton Sunstrand, 2005
    - IMAS/Pratt & Whitney, 2001
    - Electric Boat MDA layoff, 2006
    - MDA, 2006
    - Union news, 2004
    - IAM/AFL-CIO, 2006
    - IBEW, 2006
    - AFGE, 2004
    - labor, undated
    - National Association of Air Traffic Specialists, 2005
    - NAGE, 2005
    - Norwich Firefighters, 2006
    - NETU, 2006
    - Operating Engineers, 2006
    - PASS, undated
    - Fenn Manufacturing, 2003
    - Pratt & Whitney (2 folders), 2003
    - Administrative and Residual Employees Union, 2006
    - Rural Carriers (2 folders), 2005
    - Subase Union, 2004
    - Sikorsky union--Teamsters, 2006
    - SEIU, 2005
    - TORAW, 2005
    - Letter carriers, 2004
    - Postal union, 2004
    - Subase firefighters, 2003
    - Painters union, undated
    - Post offices, undated
      - Enfield
      - Bozrah
      - Brooklyn
      - Groton
      - Killingworth
      - Lebanon
      - Noank
      - Norwich (2 folders)
      - Pomfret
      - Sterling
      - Union
      - Vernon
    - CT BRAC Employees, 2003
  - Issues, International, undated (Box 24)
  - T & I committee, undated (Box 25)
  - GWOT, Clippings, Economy, 200-2006 (Box 30)
  - Clippings, Campaign Finance reform, 2001-2006 (Box 31)
  - GWOT, 2001, 2004 (Box 32)
  - Budget issues, Press releases, 2001, 2004-2006 (Box 33)
  - Football, Coast Guard Museum, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Clippings, 2000-2006 (Box 35)
    - Rowland, John (4 folders), 2003-2004
    - Accomplishments, 107th Congress, 1st session (3 folders), 2002
    - Health Care (3 folders), 2002-2004
    - Political Letters to the Editor (3 folders), 2000-2004
    - Debates, 2006
    - Politics (3 folders), 2006
    - Iraq War (3 folders), 2006
    - North Korea, 2006
  - Clippings (taxes, economy), National Security issues, 2001-2004 (Box 36)
  - GWOT, 2001-2002 (Box 37)
  - Football, 2001 March - 2002 July (Box 38)
  - Clippings (politics, economics, press releases, LTE, GWOT), 2001-2005 (Box 39)
  - Clippings (energy, immigration, general, politics, Middle East_, 2002005-2006 (Box 40)
  - Clippings, New England Dairy Compact, Istook issues, Energy, Military, Taxes, Economics, 2003-2004 (Box 41)
  - Clippings, 2002-2003 (Box 42)
  - Clippings, 2002, 2004, 2006 (Box 43)
  - LTE, Terrorism, Social Security, Taxes, Faith based issues, Speeches, undated, 2005 (Box 45)
  - BRAC, 2005-2006 (Box 46)
  - LTE, Meetings, HASC Talking points, Saddam Hussein threat, Sub base, Luntz research, 2006 (Box 47)
  - Clippings, 2005 (Box 48)
  - Energy, Defense, Crime, Stem cell, Diversity, undated, 2001 (Box 49)
  - Football, 2005 March - 2006 April (Box 50)
  - Education, Indian issues, Clippings, 2001-2002, 2005 (Box 51)
  - Clippings (general), 2001-2002 (Box 52)
  - NRCC issues, July 4th work, Briefing book, 1998, 2000, 2006 (Box 53)
  - Iraq,, House issues, 1998-2006 (Box 54)
    - Political clippings, 2006
    - Campaign clippings, 2000
    - Appropriations Requests FY 2005, 2004
    - Iraq House Armed Services Committee material, 2004
    - InterRoyal mill fire, 2005
    - Indian file with Timeline, 2002-2005
    - Iraq clippings, 2004
    - Issue Book, 1998
    - Good stuff v.2, 2002-2006
  - Towns, Norwich - Woodstock, undated (Box 55)
  - Clippings, 2006 June - October (Box 56)
  - Issues, politics, CT Peace and Justice network, Correspondence, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 57)
  - GWOT, Clippings (general), 2001-2002 (Box 58)
  - Clippings, GWOT, Economy, LTE, 2003-2006 (Box 59)
  - Football, 2002 July - 2003 November (Box 60)
  - Jeff's Issues/Company Files, A - L, undated (Box 61)
  - Issue files, A - H, undated (Box 62)
  - Clippings (politics, news, education, LTE), 2005-2006 (Box 63)
  - Football, 2003 December - 2005 March (Box 65)
  - Veterans issues, Prescription drugs, Middle East, 2001-2005 (Box 66)
  - Towns, Andover - North Stonington, undated (Box 67)
    - Andover
    - Ashford
    - Brooklyn
    - Bolton
    - Bozrah
    - Canterbury
    - Chaplin
    - Chester
    - Clinton
    - Colchester
    - Columbia
    - Coventry
    - Deep River
    - Durham
    - East Haddam
    - Eastford
    - East Lyme
    - East Hampton
    - Ellington
    - Enfield
    - Essex
    - Franklin
    - Glastonbury
    - Griswold
    - Groton
    - Haddam
    - Hampton
    - Hebron
    - Killingly
    - Killingworth
    - Lebanon
    - Ledyard
    - Lisbon
    - Lyme
    - Madison
    - Mansfield
    - Marlborough
    - Montville
    - Mystic
    - New London
    - Stonington
    - North Stonington
  - Routes 11 & 6, Campaign, Indian hearing, Ft. Trumbull, Development Plan, 2001-2002 (Box 68)
  - Speeches, Columns, District work kits, 2006 (Box 69)
  - Clippings (politics), Press releases, 2002-2003 (Box 70)
  - Environment, District work kits, 2006 (Box 71)
  - Economic-Tax issues, 2001-2002 (Box 72)
  - Communications, 2003 (Box 73)
  - Clippings (defense, war), 2002, 2006 (Box 74)
  - Homelessness, Housing, Health care, Prescription drugs, undated (Box 75)
  - Social Security, Prescription drugs, undated (Box 76)
  - Communications, 2004 (Box 77)
  - Middle East, undated (Box 78)
  - Communications, 2006 (Box 79)
  - Indian Tribal issues, undated (Box 80)
  - Press releases, Clippings (politics), 2000-2001 (Box 81)
  - Middle East, undated (Box 82)
  - Tourism, District appearances, undated (Box 83)
  - Communications, 2002 (Box 84)
  - Communications, 2006 (Box 85)
  - Videotapes, undated (Box 86)
  - Taxes/economy, 2000-2005 (Box 87)
  - Transportation, Agriculture, Fishermen, 2005-2006 (Box 88)
  - Clippings (politics), 2006 (Box 90)
  - Submarines, Eminent domain, Coast Guard, Veterans, undated (Box 91)
  - Press releases, Clippings, 2000-2001 (Box 92)
  - Clippings (politics, campaign, environment, general), SE CT corridor study, Routes 82/85/11, 1999-2006 (Box 93)
  - Indian Tribal issues hearing, 2001 February (Box 94)
  - Military, Veterans affairs, undated, 2004 (Box 95)
  - Farm issues, Businesses, FAA, District interns, undated (Box 96)
  - Education, Transportation, 2002-2003 (Box 97)
  - Jeff's Issue/Company files, L - Z, undated (Box 98)
  - Energy, undated (Box 99)
  - Reference materials for Medicare, Social SEcurity, HUD, Grants, undated (Box 100)
  - Communications, 2003 (Box 101)
  - Grants, A - Z, 2006 (Box 102)
  - Communications, 2005 (Box 103)
  - Bill research, undated (Box 104)
  - Events, 2004-2005 (Box 105)
  - Grants, A - Gl, undated (Box 108)
  - Grants, A - Z, 2006 (Box 109)
  - Events, AV, 2005-2006 (Box 110)
  - Transportation (Norwich), undated (Box 111)
  - Events, 2002-2004 (Box 112)
  - Communications, 2001 (Box 113)
  - Base Closure and Realignment files, 2005 (Box 114)
    - Navy Marine Corps Intranet system, undated
    - NSPS, undated
    - Form letters, undated
    - Office policies and guidelines, 108th Congress, undated
    - The case for Naval Submarine Base New London, Defense Base Closure and Realignment Commission, Regional hearing, Boston, MA, 2005 July 6
    - DOD Base Closure and Realignment, Report to the Commission, Dept. of the Navy, Analyses and REcommendations (v. IV), 2005 May
    - Defense Base Closure and Realignment, Report to the President, V. I, 2005
    - Defense Base Closure and Realignment, Report to the President, V. II, 2005
    - Save the Base, Press clippings, Norwich Bulletin (2 folders), 2005
    - Save the Base, Press clippings, New York Times and others, 2005
    - Save the Base, Press clippings, Hartford Courant (3 folders), 2005 May - August
    - Save the Base, Press clippings, The Day (4 folders), 2005 May - August
    - Subase New London, MILCON Brief for Rep. Simmons, 2005 February 28
    - BRAC Brief, 2005
  - BRAC, SUBASE, PPV Housing, Dredging (Norwich), undated (Box 115)
  - DC letters, Schedules, undated (Box 116)
    - Good Stuff v.1 (3 folders), 2004
    - Constituent correspondence (10 folders), 2006
    - Constituent correspondence (6 folders), 2005
  - Signed letters, undated (Box 117)
  - Tribes, Tour, Weekly reports, undated, 2001-2003 (Box 118)
  - Constituent correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 124)
    - 9 folders, 2002
    - 12 folders, 2003
  - 05-07 Earmarks, Environment, Energy (Norwich), undated (Box 127)
  - Jane's Project files, 1996-2007 (Box 128)
    - Pedestrian Bridge (New London), 1996-2004
    - New London Landmarks, 2004
    - Amtrak (3 folders), 1999-2006
    - Avery Point Lighthouse, 2004-2005
    - Ft. Trumbull, 2004-2006
    - CEDS - EDA, 2002-2004
    - Dairy Farmers, 2002-2003
    - EastConn vs. TUCCA Headstart, 2004-2005
    - Economy/Labor, 2004-2005
    - New London Housing Authority, 2004
    - Union Station, 2006
    - Dredging I-95, 2005
    - Priorities for 107th Congress, 2002
    - Homeland Security, 2003-2004
    - Multicultural Roundtable, 2004
    - Hispanic Alliance, 2002
    - El Centro, 2004
    - Suffield-Enfield-Somers Advisory Council, 2003
    - Education Roundtable, 2003-2005
    - Durham Manufacturing, 2006
    - Healthcare Roundtable, 2003-2006
    - Housing, 2002-2004
    - Long Island Sound Stewardship Act (LISSA), 2006
    - FEMA--Floods, 2005-2006
    - Connecticut Voices for Children, 2006
    - Budget vote, 2006
    - Utopia-Norwich State Hospital, 2004
    - Deployed Loved Ones, 2003
    - New Towns, 2002
    - Hurricane Katrina, 2005
    - Volunteers, 2007
    - Vernon, 2006
    - Sikorsky, 2006
    - Lego, 2006
  - Rob/Jane files, 1998-2004 (Box 130)
    - Rowland, John clippings, 2003-2004
    - Indian clippings, 2001
    - Indian clippings, reports and studies, 2002
    - Nipmuc Tribe, 2001
    - Pequot recognition, 2000
    - Indian recognition, 2002
    - 8 Mile River Project, 2000-2001
    - Minimum wage, 1998-2000
    - Plum Island, 2002
    - U.S. Census Bureau report, 2004
  - Press Binders, undated (Box 131)
  - Grant files S - W, Campaign and Issues, 2001-2007 (Box 132)
    - Safe Foundation, 2003
    - Safer (Letter), 2004 September 29
    - Salt Island Overlook (Westbrook), 2003 June 5
    - Salt Marsh Opera, 2005 May 2
    - Science Epicenter and DNA Learning Center, 2004
    - Scotland Volunteer Fire Department, 2004 April 23
    - Sea Research Foundation, Mystic, 2004 August 23
    - Seder Property, 2003 September 19
    - SEIU Meeting, 2005 February 25
    - Silvered Electronic MICA Company--SEMCO, 2003 April 21
    - Southeast Connecticut Enterprise Reguion, Inc., New London, 2003-2004
    - South Killingly Fire Department, 2004 October 8
    - Sccog, 2004 May 26
    - National Endowment for the Arts, 2003 July 17
    - Sterling Fire Department, 2003 April 2
    - Stafford Public Schools, 2002 October 1
    - Sterling Schools and EastConn, 2003 July 7
    - Stonington Fire Department, 2003 April 30
    - Stonington Food Coop, 2003 April 15
    - Stonington USDA Rural Development, 2004 August 26
    - Suffield Cops in Schools, 2004 March 26
    - Suffield Senior Center, 2003-2004
    - Suffield Connecticut Department of Social Services, 2003 April 17
    - Survivors of Homicide, 2004 April 23
    - Teaching American History Grant, 2003 May 7
    - Three Rivers Community College, 2002-2003
    - Tolland Community Children's Center, 2004 August 12
    - Thompsonville Fire District #2, 2003-2004
    - Townshend-Forest legacy, 2003 September 19
    - USAID-Tsunami, 2005
    - Transportation Safety, 2003
    - Tri-Town Youth Services, 2003 February 3
    - Trust for Public Lands, 2004 September 8
    - Tutoring for Success (Frank Loomis Palmer Fund, 2003 May 22
    - TUCCA Headstart, 2003 March 20
    - United Cerebral Palsy Association of Southeastern Connecticut, 2003 August 27
    - UConn Grant awards, 2004
    - UConn Grants, 2003
    - UConn Homer Babbidge Library, 2004
    - UConn; NASA, 2007 July 28
    - Vernon Community Health Center, 2003 February 5
    - Vernon Fire Department, 2003 April 22
    - Vernon Housing and Development Corporation, 2002 December
    - Vertigo, Inc. Spave HAB/Texas, 2004 September 1
    - Voluntwon Volunteer Fire Company, 2004 March 24
    - Wesleyan Upward Bound, 2002 November 27
    - Westbrook Fire Department, 2003 May 5
    - West Thompson Independent Fire Company, 2004 April 6
    - Williamantic Fire Department FEMA, 2002 August 27
    - Willington Senior Housing, 2004 June 9
    - WINCOG Meeting, 2004 June 4
    - Windham Center Fire Department, 2004 April 9
    - Willimantic/Plainfield Chaplin Corporation, 2003 May
    - Windham School Readiness Council, 2005 July 15
    - Windham Drug Free Community Grant, 2004
    - Windham WPCA, 2007 July 30
    - Windham and EastConn Teaching American History Grant, 2003-2004
    - Women's Business Development Center, 2004 April 21
    - Woodstock Volunteer Volunteer Fire Association, 2003 May 9
    - Windham/Willimantic Community Support program Grant, 2003 May 7
    - Woodstock Academy, 2003 August 27
    - Woodstock Volunteer Fire Association, 2004 April 16
    - Irving August Grant Request, 2002 August 21
    - Federal Victims Fund, undated
    - Red Cross, undated
    - victims Compensation
      - Terrorist victims, 2001
      - Federal Victims Fund, 2002
      - Victims Compensation fund, 2002
      - McCourt Garden, 2003
      - Piver Family, 2002 Janaury 14
      - Families/Agencies meeting, 2001 December 17
      - Catholic charities, 2001-2003
      - Office of Victim Services, 2003
      - Red Cross, 2003
      - Garba, 2001 December 18
    - Campaign/Election
      - Election Media, 2002
      - Campaign media, 2004
      - Job descriptions and policies, 108th Congress, 2003-2004
  - 9/11, EB, Campaign/Elections, Transportation, 1999-2006 (Box 133)
    - Electric Boat
      - Contracts, 2004
      - Fliers, 2004
      - Smith Act, 2004
      - List of Clearances, 2004
      - Kevin Cassidy, Director of Security, 2004
      - General Cunningham, DSS, 2001
      - Snuffy Smith/Ken Dalacruz, 2001 May
      - DSS, 2001
      - Lee Schachter, Dir. Doha, 2002
      - Stephen Lewis, Carol Wilson, 2001
      - DSS/OPM Shrft, 2003-2004
      - DSS/OPM Stop Clearances, 2006
      - Clearances and labor, 2004
      - Security Clearance Press, 2003-2006
      - Lists of Names for Clearance, 2004
      - Agents' Complaints, 2005
    - Route 11
      - 2001-2004
      - 2005
      - Opposition, 2003
      - Greenway Bill, 2003
      - Impact Minimization Study and Map, 1999 June
      - Draft Environmental Impact Statment and Section 4(f) Evaluation, 1999
      - Community-Sensitive Upgrade Study, 2006
    - Transportation Issues, 2003-2006
      - Dairy Marketing Services, 2003 August 5
      - Amalgamated Transit Union, 2006 March 6
      - Association of Flight Attendants, 2006 March 15
      - South Maple Street Bridge, 2006 May 24
      - DMV-Single State Registration System, 2006 July 12
      - Homeland Security, 2006
    - Service Animals, 2006 August 11
    - American Federation of Government Employees (AFGE), 2006
  - Dear Colleague Letters, 2001, 2004 (Box 134)
    - 3 folders, 2001
    - 11 folders, 2004
  - Rob letters/Press, undated, 2002-2006 (Box 135)
    - Press releases (2 folders), 2004
    - Submarien Trade press, 2006 February - March
    - Clippings--Ports, CGA, Tiawan, Sikorsky, 2006 january - February
    - Cosponsors/Letters, 2003
    - Bills sponsored by RS (2 folders), 2005
    - Clippings--Blunt, Shadegg, 2005
    - NSA Terrorist Surveillance program, undated
    - Thank you letters (2 folders), 2003-2005
    - Letters signed by RS (3 folders), 2005
    - Letters signed by RS, 109th Congress, 2nd Session (3 folders), 2006
    - Constituent correspondence (3 folders), 2002
    - Constituent correspondence (3 folders), 2002-2003
  - Research files, undated (Box 136)
  - (Box 137)
  - DC letters, schedules, 2003-2006 (Box 138)
    - Constituent correspondence (12 folders), 2005
    - Constituent correspondence (3 folders), 2004
    - Press releases (2 folders), 2003
    - Calendar, 2006
    - Rob's schedule (2 folders), 2005-2006
    - Flag requests (2 folders), 2003-2005
  - Transportation, Scouts, undated, 2000-2003 (Box 139)
    - Eagle Scouts 3 (3 folders), undated
    - CT Rail concerns/issues, undated
    - Poughkeepsie Bridge, undated
    - Amtrak and Mystic, undated
    - Chemical-rail issues, undated
    - Amtrak whistles, undated
    - Amtrak and Enfield, undated
    - Amtrak, undated
    - Providence and Worcester Railroad Company, undated
    - Friends of the High Line, undated
    - Freight Rail, undated
    - L. Lynam Meeting, undated
    - Remote Control Locomotives, undated
    - High Speed Rail, undated
    - Amtrak Bailout/Reauthorization, 2002, 2003
    - Amtrak Reform, undated
    - Amtrak, undated
    - Rail Labor, undated
    - Amtrak Reform Council (ARC, 2 folders), 2000-2002
    - National Association of Railroad Passengers, 2002
    - H.R. 2950, Ride 21, undated
    - Highway Funding Restoration, undated
    - Sec. 4(F), undated
    - Streetlights Bill, undated
    - Vets CDL Bill, undated
    - Route 6, undated
    - Route 6 Field Hearing, undated
  - BRAC, 2005 (Box 140)
    - Dept. of Defense, Base Closure and Realignment Report, V.I, Part 1 of 2: Results and Process (5 folders), 2005 May
    - The Submarien Capital of the World, The Case for Naval Submarien Base New London (SUBASE NLON) (5 folders), 2005 July 6
    - Mobile Targets from Under the Sea, New Submarine Missions in the New Security Environment (7 folders), undated
    - Base Realignment and Closure, Reports and clippings (14 folders), 2005 March - August
  - BRAC, Cosponsored Bills, Signed letters, 2001-2006 (Box 141)
    - BRAC: Reports and Clippings (2 folders), 2005 August
    - BRAC: Reports and Clippings, 2005 September-November, 2006 August
    - Education, Energy/Environment, Labor, Miscellaneous, Terrorism, Veterans, 2004
    - Appropriations, 2001
    - Defense, 2001
    - Energy/Environment, 2001
    - Health, 2001
    - Labor, 2001
    - Miscellaneous, 2001
    - Social Security, 2001
    - Taxes, 2001
    - Terrorism, 2001
    - Transportation, 2001
    - Veterans, 2001
    - Signed letters, 2002
      - Agriculture
      - Appropriations
      - Defense
      - Energy/Environment
      - Foreign Affairs
      - Health
      - Labor
      - Miscellaneous
      - Social Security
      - Taxes
      - Transportation
      - Veterans
    - Signed letters, 2003
      - Agriculture
      - Animal
      - Defense
      - Education
      - Energy/Environment (2 folders)
      - Foreign Affairs
      - health
      - Indians
      - Labor
      - Miscellaneous
      - Taxes
      - Terrorism
      - Transportation
      - Veterans
    - Signed letters, 2004
      - Appropriations
      - Defense
      - Education
      - Energy/Environment
      - Foreign Affairs
      - Indians
      - Labor
      - Miscellaneous
      - Taxes